

# ANJALI KUMARAN

LEADERSHIP | STRATEGY | WRITING | FACILITATION

Profile

I am a well-rounded individual with professional experience that allows me to bring a fresh and diverse perspective to any project. I have extensive experience with leadership and project management, as well as coordination, and more recently, web and product design.

### EXPERIENCE

#### UC SAN DIEGO ORIENTATION LEADER

Student Leadership at Eleanor Roosevelt College

#### **2023 - Present**

- Facilitating new student groups and leading campus tours.
- Extensive leadership and facilitation training and workshops.
- Writing, recording, coordinating and participating in welcome-week performances.

#### **RAINBOW ALLIANCE FOUNDER & PRESIDENT**

Founded and Led MISP's First Gender-Sexuality Alliance

#### 2021-2023

- Organized and led fundraising events to raise \$5000+ for breast cancer research and LGBTQIA+ Rights organizations.
- Worked with advisors and school administration to raise awareness and create space within the community.

#### **GYLS CONFERENCE EXECUTIVE**

Pan-Asian Youth Leadership Summit Management

#### 2021-2022

- Conducted interviews and led skill-assessment in the selection process for the conference secretariat.
- Leveraged unique perspective to establish conference structure and tailor content to the target demographic.
- Worked alongside an international team to advertise, manage and execute a successful conference.



123-456-7899



john.doe@gmail.com



9500 Gilman Dr, La Jolla, San Diego



https://github.com/Anjali-Kumaran/AnjaliKCOGS3FinalProject.git

### EDUCATION

## INTERNATIONAL BACCALAUREATE DIPLOMA

Mahindra International School, Pune IBDP Certificate.

2020-2023

## COGNITIVE & BEHAVIORAL NEUROSCIENCE

University of California San Diego, Bachelors Degree

2023 - Present

## SKILLS

- Design Thinking
- Facilitation and Integration
- Problem-Solving
- Team Leadership
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication
- Writing and Outreach
- Advertising and Awareness
- Working with Diverse Teams